

1800 102 2558 | +91 9818882211





AMBICA MANGALAGIRI Featured

 $\label{linux} \mbox{ System Administrator, Seeking roles in System Administration, Application}$

Development, Application Support, IT Project Mgmt, Requirement

Gathering, Configuration Mgmt, Linux System Administration, Server

Administration, Data Structures, Redhat Linux

Current Designation: Linux System Administrator Total Experience: 6 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Infosys Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad Highest Degree: MTech [Computers]

Pref. Location: Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance
Role: System Admin

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: linux system administrator, application development, application support, it project mgmt, requirement gathering, configuration mgmt, linux system administration, server administration, data structures, redhat linux, wmware, Devops, Ansible, Jenkins

Innux,vmware,Devops,Ansible,Jenkins

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 27-Sep-20 Last Modified: 27-Sep-20

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills

Summary

8 years of total IT experience as a Linux System Administrator

Installation of Linux operating system locally and over network.

Configuring and sharing files through NFS and FTP server into the environment.

Configuring Samba server and adding windows clients to share files through samba.

Creating and managing Linux file system spaces.

Creating and managing LVM for the clients and reducing/extending LVM as per client's requirement.

Creating and maintaining Linux based user's and groups.

Configuring network bonding for maintaining network redundancy to the servers

Technically proficient with knowledge: Red Hat 6&7, Shell scripting, Amazon Web Services- EC2, VPC, IAM Portal, Cloud Watch VMware.

Technically proficient with knowledge :Shell scripting-Quotes, Input, Output & Filters, Variables,

Functions, conditions, Loops, EVAL, Type.

Tecnically proficient with Knowledge: VMWare-ESXI, V-Motion, HA, DRS, FT and related VMware features, P2v, V2p, Veem Backup and Replication

Work Experience

- Infosys as Linux System Administrator Jan 2017 to Till Date
- Infosys as Linux System Administrator Jan 2017 to Jan 2017

Jan 2017-till date
Name of Employer
Project
Support & Maintenance
Work Location
Designation
Client
Linux System Administrator
Infosys, Hyderabad
Infosys, Hyderabad
Infosys, Hyderabad
Infosys, Hyderabad
Technology Analyst
Capital Group

Roles and Responsibilities:

Responsible for server provisioning, configuration, maintenance and enhancement

of Unix/Linux servers.

Responding to server related issues and providing resolution to the customer.

Incident and Change Management

Requirement gathering from the customer for enhancing the application and customizing as per client requirements.

Responsible for deployment of code and server decommissions.

Providing support and maintenance of existing applications functionality.

Work includes server builds, software installations etc.

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld. Package installation through Yum and RPM
Upgrading the latest Patches and Packages on release basis.
Updating Alert management report.
Sharing the NFS and NAS mount points and troubleshooting the NFS/NAS issues.

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: graduation (computers) from From Kavitha Memorial Degree&PG college, khammam in 2004 PG: M.Tech (Computers) from Sri Indu College of Engineering, Hyderabad in 2010

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Linux, Windows			
redhat, VMware			
BMC			
SHELL			
C,DATA STRUCTURES			
EC2,S3,RDS,IAM			

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient	✓	✓	✓
Hindi	Beginner	✓	✓	✓
Telugu	Expert	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.